Pandering is not the answer, but how do you compliment a man who catches your eye?
You want to do that, I'm sure.
This is Dr. Paul, author of Boomer Girls.
And the key to that is sincerity.
Everyone finds a phony not to their liking.
You want to make certain that compliment you give that man is real and right on.
A lot of times it's pretty easy.
You can say, I saw you drive up in that car.
It looks like you keep it really clean.
The guy will love that.
Of course he does.
Maybe he has something on his shirt.
A university that he went to.
Did you go to Notre Dame?
I went there for a football game once.
A compliment.
That's a compliment in a subtle.
Direct compliments can be fine--again, they have to be sincere.
Make certain that when you make that compliment, it's also one that can be taken in a different way--a slant to it.
What do you think of that Notre Dame football team?
And he's on.
He's there.
And what you want to do--you want to open the conversation.
That's what a compliment is all about.
He caught your eye.
Give him a compliment.
This is Dr. Paul.
May your fantasies of today be your realities of tomorrow.